(Leonard:)Mm, this one comes with
music and flowers.
(Leonard:)Oh, they even stream the whole
thing live on the Internet.
(Penny:)Why would we want that?
'Cause there's a lot
of gorgeous blondes out there
(Leonard:)who don't believe they can land
a short, nearsighted scientist.
(Leonard:)Let's give them hope.
(Penny:)Whatever. Put us
on the Internet.
(Penny:)I've always wanted a wedding
with a comment section.
I-If you're not into this,
we can do it another time.
(Penny:)No. No, I want to.
(Penny:)Look, we've put this
off long enough.
(Penny:)Let's do it.
Aw.
(Leonard:)That's exactly what you said the
first time we slept together.
(ringtone playing)
(Leonard:)Oh, excuse me.
(Leonard:)Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Hey.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, have you
gotten married yet?
(Leonard:)No. Why?
Good. Don't do it!
Why not?
(Sheldon:)Some important new information
has come to light.
(Sheldon:)Women are the worst.
(Sheldon:)I thought it was paper cuts,
but I was wrong.
(Sheldon:)No piece of paper
ever cut me this deep.
(Leonard:)What happened now?
(Sheldon:)Amy has ended our relationship.
(Leonard:)Oh, no. Seriously?
(Penny:)What's going on?